A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Cox and Reece Investigations FA418
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Washington D. C. Files, 3; 16.32 Cubic Feet 38 letter document boxes, 3 legal document boxes and 2 half-legal boxes
  - C-3A-Fellowship Directory Supplements, 1915-1954 (Box 41, Folder 773)
  - C-4-International Health Division Fellows, 1946-1950 (Box 41, Folder 774)
  - C-4-International Health Division Fellows, 1951-1953 (Box 41, Folder 775)
  - C-5-Grants to Individuals and Organizations in Iron Curtain Countries, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 776)
  - C-5A-Fellowships: Tabulation by Type of Action and Division, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 777)
  - C-6-Books Published as the Result of Rockefeller Foundation Grants, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 778)
  - C-6A-Outstanding Fellows, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 779)
  - C-6B-Outstanding Fellows, Supporting Material, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 780)
  - C-7-Excerpts from the Presidents Annual Review, 1920-1954 (Box 42, Folder 781)
  - C-7-EXHIBIT, The Rockefeller Foundation, Grants to Institutions, Individuals and Projects, 1936-1952, 1936-1939 (Box 42, Folder 782)
  - C-7-EXHIBIT, The Rockefeller Foundation, Grants to Institutions, Individuals and Projects, 1936-1952, 1940-1944 (Box 42, Folder 783)
  - C-7-EXHIBIT, The Rockefeller Foundation, Grants to Institutions, Individuals and Projects, 1936-1952, 1945-1948 (Box 42, Folder 784)
  - C-7-EXHIBIT, The Rockefeller Foundation, Grants to Institutions, Individuals and Projects, 1936-1952, 1949-1952 (Box 43, Folder 785)
  - C-7-EXHIBIT, The Rockefeller Foundation, Grants to Institutions, Individuals and Projects, 1936-1952, 1936-1943 (Box 43, Folder 786)
  - C-7-EXHIBIT, The Rockefeller Foundation, Grants to Institutions, Individuals and Projects, 1936-1952, 1944-1952 (Box 43, Folder 787)
  - C-8-Rockefeller Foundation Quarterly Reports, 1950-1954 (Box 43, Folder 788)
  - C-9f-Rockefeller Foundation Minutes RE: Grants to China Medical Board, 1928-1954 (Box 43, Folder 789)
  - C-9g-Counsel's Work File, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 790)
  - C-9h1-9-China Medical Board and Peiking Union Medical College, 1928-1952 (Box 43, Folder 791)
  - C-9h10-China: 1914-1951: Vol. I, 1915-1917 Index (Box 44, Folder 792)
  - C-9h10-China: 1914-1951: Vol. II, 1918-1921 (Box 44, Folder 793)
  - C-9h10-China: 1914-1951: Vol. III, 1922-1924 (Box 44, Folder 794)
  - C-9h10-China: 1914-1951: Vol. IV, 1925-1929 (Box 44, Folder 795)
  - C-9h10-China: 1914-1951: Vol. V, 1930-1934 (Box 45, Folder 796)
  - C-9h10-China: 1914-1951: Vol. VI, 1935-1936 (Box 45, Folder 797)
  - C-9h10-China: 1914-1951: Vol. VII, 1937-1938 (Box 45, Folder 798)
  - C-9h10-China: 1914-1951: Vol. VIII, 1939-1942 (Box 46, Folder 799)
  - C-9h10-China: 1914-1951: Vol. IX, 1943-1950 (Box 46, Folder 800)
  - C-9i-Excerpts From Fosdick's History of Rockefeller Foundation RE: China (Box 46, Folder 801)
  - C-10-Geographical Listing of institutions Receiving Support from The Rockefeller Foundation through 1953 December 31, 1953-1954 (Box 46, Folder 802)
  - C-10A-Number of Institutions per State Aided by Rockefeller Foundation and General Education Board, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 803)
  - C-11a-Division of Humanities and General, 1952 July 1-1953 December 31 (Box 46, Folder 804A)
  - C-11a-Division of Humanities and General, 1952 July 1-1953 December 31 (Box 46, Folder 804B)
  - C-11b-Division of Medicine and Public Health, 1952 July 1-1953 December 31 (Box 47, Folder 805A)
  - C-11b-Division of Medicine and Public Health, 1952 July 1-1953 December 31 (Box 47, Folder 805B)
  - C-11c-Division of Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1952 July 1-1953 December 31 (Box 47, Folder 806A)
  - C-11c-Division of Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1952 July 1-1953 December 31 (Box 47, Folder 806B)
  - C-11c-Division of Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1952 July 1-1953 December 31 (Box 47, Folder 806C)
  - C-11d-Division of Social Sciences, 1952 July 1-1953 December 31 (Box 48, Folder 807A)
  - C-11d-Division of Social Sciences, 1952 July 1-1953 December 31 (Box 48, Folder 807B)
  - C-11e-Actions of the Rockefeller Foundation, 1954 January-April 30 (Box 48, Folder 808)
  - C-12a-Rockefeller Foundation Actions Concerning the American Council on Education, American Council of Learned Societies, American Historical Association, Institute of International Education, 1913-1954 May (Box 48, Folder 809)
  - C-12b-RF Actions Concerning the National Council of the Churches of Christ, National Education Association, National Research Council, 1913-1954 May (Box 49, Folder 810)
  - C-12c-RF Actions Concerning the Social Science Research Council, 1913-1954 May (Box 49, Folder 811)
  - C-13-Matching Grants (Box 49, Folder 812)
  - C-14-General Grants of $250,000 or More, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 813)
  - C-15-Geographical Distribution of Natural Sciences Program, 1932-1948 (Box 49, Folder 814)
  - C-16-Grants Lapsed, 1913-1952 (Box 49, Folder 815)
  - C-17-Grants to University of Chicago, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 816)
  - C-18-Rockefeller Foundation and General Education Board Grants to Tax Supported Agencies, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 817)
  - C-19, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 818)
  - C-20-Grants Through Fiscal Agents (Box 49, Folder 819)
  - C-21-Grants for Work in Foreign Countries (Rockefeller Foundation and General Education Board), 1954 (Box 49, Folder 820)
  - D-1-Rockefeller Foundation Policy on Grants to Communists, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 821)
  - D-1A-Rockefeller Foundation Policy on Grants to Communists, Supporting Memoranda, 1928-1952 (Box 49, Folder 822)
  - D-1B-Material RE: Relations Between United States and Russia, 1947-1952 (Box 49, Folder 823)
  - D-1C-Outline of Post war Political- Events in Iron Curtain Countries, 1944-1952 (Box 49, Folder 824)
  - D-2-Examples of Extreme Use of Term "Subversive", 1951-1961 (Box 49, Folder 825)
  - D-3-Legistative and Judicial Definitions of "Subversive", 1945-1953 (Box 50, Folder 826)
  - D-3A-Memo RE: Subversive Activities Control Act, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 827)
  - D-4a-Executive Orders, 1947-1953 (Box 50, Folder 828)
  - D-4b-Attorney General's List, 1950-1954 (Box 50, Folder 829)
  - D-4c-Loyalty and Security in the State Department, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 830)
  - D-4d-Senate Committee Proof That the Communist Party Conspires to Use Violence, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 831)
  - D-5a-Guide to Subversive Organizations (Box 50, Folder 832)
  - D-5b-Index IV and V to Committee Publications and List of Reports, undated (Box 50, Folder 833)
  - D-5c-Criticisms and Citations of House Un-American Activities Committee - Rockefeller Foundation Grants, 1938-1950 (Box 50, Folder 834)
  - D-5d-Index IV and V to House Un-American Activites Committee (Box 50, Folder 835)
  - D-6A-Functions and Procedures of Administrative Agencies, 1946 (Box 50, Folder 836)
  - D-7-Grant Declined Upon Investigation Disclosing Communist Affiliation, 1950-1952 (Box 50, Folder 837)
  - D-8a-Statement by Rusk before Cox Committee, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 838)
  - D-8b-Summary of Grants and Rhind Statement, 1935-1951 (Box 50, Folder 839)
  - D-8c-Excerpts from Annual Reports, 1929-1950 (Box 50, Folder 840)
  - D-8d-List of Publications, 1925-1952 (Box 50, Folder 841)
  - D-8e-The Rockefeller Foundation, Grants to The Institute of Pacific Relations, 1926-1939 (Box 50, Folder 842)
  - D-8e-The Rockefeller Foundation, Grants to The Institute of Pacific Relations, 1940-1951 (Box 50, Folder 843)
  - D-8f-Report No. 2050 of Senate Subcommittee on Internal Security: Institute of Pacific Relations, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 844)
  - D-8g-Criticisms and Citations from Senate Report No. 2050: Rockefeller Foundation Grants (Box 51, Folder 845)
  - D-8h-Institute of Pacific Relations: Published Criticisms, 1950-1952 (Box 51, Folder 846)
  - D-8i-Counsel's Work File, 1946-1954 (Box 51, Folder 847)
  - D-8j-Evans File on Statements, 1951-1953 (Box 51, Folder 848)
  - D-8k-The Rockefeller Foundation and The Institute of Pacific Relations: Statement of 1952 October 10, 1952-1954 (Box 51, Folder 849)
  - D-10-Security, Loyalty and Science: Gellhorn, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 850)
  - D-11-Grants to Known or Alleged Communists and Ex-Communists, 1933-1952 (Box 51, Folder 851)
  - D-12-Grants to Individuals Politically Questionable, 1925-1953 (Box 51, Folder 852)
  - D-13-Americans for Intellectual Freedom: Ex-Sponsors Waldorf Peace Conference, 1949-1952 (Box 51, Folder 853)
  - D-14-Illinois Seditions Activities Investigation Commission, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 854)
  - D-15-Evaluation of Persons Listed in Answers to Cox Questionnaire, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 855)
  - E-1-The Rockefeller Boards and Education in the United States (Box 51, Folder 856)
  - E-2-War Work of Rockefeller Foundation: Fosdick, 1943 (Box 51, Folder 857)
  - E-2A-War Work of Rockefeller Foundation: Correspondence, 1943 (Box 51, Folder 858)
  - E-3-Grants for Russian Studies and Publications, 1934-1952 (Box 51, Folder 859)
  - E-4-Rockefeller Foundation, General Education Board and Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorail Grants in Tennessee, 1913-1953 (Box 51, Folder 860)
  - F-1a-d-Rockefeller Foundation Mexican Agricultural Program (Box 51, Folder 861)
  - F-2a-b-Operating Procedures for Overseas Personnel, 1946-1952 (Box 51, Folder 862)
  - F-3-Overseas Personnel in Division of Medicine and Public Health and Division of Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1952-1954 (Box 51, Folder 863)
  - F-4-Grants to Russian Organizations, Individuals and Refugees, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 864)
  - G-1-Charitable Trust Regulation in Great Britain, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 865)
  - G-2-Examples of "Dead-Hand" Control Funds (Box 51, Folder 866)
  - G-3-Statistics on United States Education from Rockefeller Foundation and Government Research, 1900-1952 (Box 51, Folder 867)
  - G-3A-Government Reports on Education and Scientific Research, 1945-1953 (Box 52, Folder 868)
  - G-4a-g-Books on Philanthropy (Box 52, Folder 869)
  - G-5-Memorandum RE: Research in Europe Gerard R. Pomerot and Warren Weaver to Lindsley F. Kimball, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 870)
  - G-6a-Carnegie Corporation, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 871)
  - G-6b-Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1952-1953 (Box 52, Folder 872)
  - G-6c-W. K. Kellogg Foundation, 1952-1953 (Box 52, Folder 873)
  - G-6d-Alfed P. Sloan Foundation, Inc., 1951-1952 (Box 52, Folder 874)
  - H-1a1-"Headlines", 1938-1954 (Box 52, Folder 875)
  - H-1a2-"Counterattack", 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 876)
  - H-1a3-"American Legion Magazine", 1948-1954 (Box 52, Folder 877)
  - H-1a4-"Friends of Public Schools", 1949 (Box 52, Folder 878)
  - H-1a5-"Timid Billion" by Edwin R. Embree, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 879)
  - H-1a6-Human Events, 1952-1954 (Box 53, Folder 880)
  - H-1a7-Educational Reviewer, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 881)
  - H-1a8-United Evangelical Action, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 882)
  - H-1b1-Miscellaneous, 1938-1955 (Box 53, Folder 883)
  - H-1b2-Business Connections of Rockefeller Foundation, 1940-1954 (Box 53, Folder 884)
  - H-1b3-Tax Exemption, 1934-1954 (Box 53, Folder 885)
  - H-1b4-Institute of Pacific Relations, 1950-1954 (Box 53, Folder 886)
  - H-1b5-Influence on Educational Institutions, 1935-1953 (Box 53, Folder 887)
  - H-1b6-Langer History, 1947-1954 (Box 53, Folder 888)
  - H-1b7-Internationalism, 1939-1954 (Box 53, Folder 889)
  - H-1b8-The Press, 1948-1954 (Box 53, Folder 890)
  - H-1b9-Civil Liberties Study, 1949-1952 (Box 53, Folder 891)
  - H-1c1 Books-"The Rockefeller Internationalism", 1952 (Box 53, Folder 892)
  - H-1c2 Books-"The Drug Story", 1949 (Box 53, Folder 893)
  - H-1c3 Books-"Prejudice and the Press", 1950 (Box 53, Folder 894)
  - H-1c4 Books-"Your Life is Their Toy", 1940 (Box 53, Folder 895)
  - H-1c5 Books-"Money to Burn", 1938 (Box 53, Folder 896)
  - H-1c6-"Stalin's Choice for President", Josephson, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 897)
  - H-1d-Congressional Record and Comments, 1951 August 1; 1952 April 4 (Box 53, Folder 898)
  - H-1e-Criticisms of Rockefeller Foundation in Russian Press, 1947-1953 (Box 54, Folder 899)
  - H-2-Walsh Committee Reports, 1915-1954 (Box 54, Folder 900)
  - H-3-"The Story of the Rockefeller Foundation" Fosdick, Raymond B., 1952 (Box 54, Folder 901)
  - H-4-Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memoiral Annual and Final Reports, 1922-1928 (Box 54, Folder 902)
  - H-4A-Statement RE: Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial, 1952-1954 (Box 54, Folder 903)
  - H-4B-Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memoiral Report on Grants (Box 54, Folder 904)
  - H-5-Spellman Fund Final Report, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 905)
  - H-6a-General Statement (Box 54, Folder 906)
  - H-6b-Gregg Memo, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 907)
  - H-6c-"Sexual Behavior in the Human Male", Kinsey, Alfred C., 1948 (Box 54, Folder 908)
  - H-6d-"Sexual Behavior in the Human Female", Kinsey, Alfred C., 1953 (Box 55, Folder 909)
  - H-6e-Reviews and Commentary, 1953-1954 (Box 55, Folder 910)
  - H-6f-Kinsey's File of Reviews, 1948-1954 (Box 55, Folder 911)
  - H-6g-Correspondence, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 912)
  - H-6h-Drew Pearson Broadcast Item, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 913)
  - H-6i-Correspondence Rusk and Dodd (Box 55, Folder 914)
  - H-6j-Clippings, 1947-1954 (Box 55, Folder 915)
  - H-6k-Morison Memo on History of Resistance to Scientific Advances, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 916)
  - H-7-Report of Hamburg Congress on Science and Freedom, 1953 (Box 55, Folder 917)
  - H-8-Amerasia Case, 1945-1952 (Box 55, Folder 918)
  - H-9-Eisenhower Speeches, I, 1952 September 21-October 15 (Box 55, Folder 919)
  - H-9-Eisenhower Speeches, II, 1952 October 16-November 4 (Box 55, Folder 920)
  - H-10-International Character of Science, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 921)
  - H-11-Miscellaneous "Quotables", 1936-1954 (Box 56, Folder 922)
  - I-1-Resolutions, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 923)
  - I-2-Questionnaire and Cox Letter of Transmittal, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 924)
  - I-2A-Questionionnaire: Work Copies 1-49, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 925)
  - I-3-Answers of The Rockefeller Foundation to ?Questionnaire Submitted by the Select Committee of the House of Representatives of the Congress of the United States, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 926)
  - I-3-Answers to the General Education Board to Questionnaire Submitted by the Select Committee of the House of Representatives of the Congress of the United States, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 927)
  - I-3A (Box 56, Folder 927A)
  - I-3B-Answer to Questionnaire-Index, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 928)
  - I-4a-Committee Members and Staff: Who?s Who (Box 56, Folder 929)
  - I-4b-Committee Members and Staff-Keele, 1952-1955 (Box 56, Folder 930)
  - I-5b-Correspondence: Trustees and Field Staff, 1952-1953 (Box 56, Folder 931)
  - I-5c-Fowler, Leva, Hawes and Symington Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 56, Folder 932)
  - I-5d-Correspondence: General, 1951-1953 (Box 57, Folder 933)
  - I-5e-Secretary's File RE: Inquiry, 1951-1952 (Box 57, Folder 934)
  - I-6a-Press Clippings, 1951-1952 (Box 57, Folder 935)
  - I-6b-Ripley Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 57, Folder 936)
  - I-7-Guggenheim Foundation Answer to Questionnaire, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 937)
  - I-8a-Sugarman Statements on Tax Exemption (Box 57, Folder 938)
  - I-8b-Statements and Related Correspondence: Fosdick, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 939)
  - I-8c-Statements and Related Correspondence: Myers, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 940)
  - I-8d-Statement and Related Correspondence: John D. Rockefeller, 3rd, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 941)
  - I-8e-Statement and Related Correspondence: Rusk: Institute of Pacific Relations (Box 57, Folder 942)
  - I-8f-Statement and Related Correspondence: Simmons, Harvard School of Public Health, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 943)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 1, 1952 November 18 (Box 58, Folder 944)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 2, 1952 November 19 (Box 58, Folder 945)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 3, 1952 November 20 (Box 58, Folder 946)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 4, 1952 November 21 (Box 58, Folder 947)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 5, 1952 November 24 (Box 58, Folder 948)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 6, 1952 November 25 (Box 58, Folder 949)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 7, 1952 December 2 (Box 58, Folder 950)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 8, 1952 December 3 (Box 59, Folder 951)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 9, 1952 December 5 (Box 59, Folder 952)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 10, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 953)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 11, 1952 December 9 (Box 59, Folder 954)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 12 and 13, 1952 December 10; December 11 1952 (Box 59, Folder 955)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 14 and 15, 1952 December 15; December 17 1952 (Box 59, Folder 956)
  - I-9-Hearings Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, Vol 16, 17 and 18, 1952 December 22; 23; December 30 1952 (Box 59, Folder 957)
  - I-9A-Tax-Exempt Foundations, Hearing Before the Select Committee to Investigate Tax-Exempt Foundations and Comparable Organizations, House of Representatives, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 958)
  - I-9B-Final Report, 1952-1953 (Box 60, Folder 959)
  - I-9C-Questions Excerpted From Transcript, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 960)
  - I-10-Rusk's Notes on Congressional Investigation From Trustees Monthly Report, 1953 January 1 (Box 60, Folder 961)
  - I-11-Preparation for Cox Investigation, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 962)
  - I-12-Documents for Use at Hearing (List) (Box 60, Folder 963)
  - J-1-Resolutions, 1953-1954 (Box 60, Folder 964)
  - J-1a-Resolutions: Taxation, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 965A)
  - J-1a-General Education Board, Report to the Special Committee of the House of Representatives to Investigate Tax Exempt Foundations, 1953-1954 (Box 60, Folder 965B-C)
  - J-1a-General Education Board, Report to the Special Committee of the House of Representatives to Investigate Tax Exempt Foundations, 1953-1954 (Box 61, Folder 965)
  - J-1a-Worksheets (Miscellaneous), 1953-1954 (Box 61, Folder 965E)
  - J-2-Reece Speech: Congressional Record, 1953 April 23 (Box 61, Folder 966)
  - J-2A-Other References in Congressional Record, 1953 July 27 (Box 61, Folder 967)
  - J-3a-Committee Members and Staff: Who's Who (Box 61, Folder 968)
  - J-3b-Committee Members and Staff: Dodd Correspondence (Box 61, Folder 969)
  - J-3c-Committee Members and Staff: College Affiliations of Members, 1953-1954 (Box 61, Folder 970)
  - J-3d-Information About Members, 1953-1955 (Box 61, Folder 971)
  - J-4-Dodd Letter, 1953 December 3, Asking Data on Grants, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 972)
  - J-4A-Report to Committee with Breakdown on "Self-Administered" Grants, 1953-1954 (Box 61, Folder 973A)
  - J-4 -, 1913-1953 (Box 61, Folder 973B)
  - J-4B-Report to Committee: Working File, 1953-1954 (Box 62, Folder 974)
  - J-4C-Report to the Committee with Appropriation Numbers, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 975)
  - J-5-Rusk Letter to Wormser Origin of Grants and Memorandum, undated (Box 62, Folder 976)
  - J-5A-Background Material on Origin of Grants, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 977)
  - J-6a-Report to Committee: Norman Dodd, 1953-1954 (Box 62, Folder 978)
  - J-6b-Report to Committee: McNiece, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 979)
  - J-6c-Report to Committee: Kathryn Casey, 1963-1964 (Box 62, Folder 980)
  - J-7a-Statement before Committee: Arthur S. Adams: American Council on Education, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 981)
  - J-7b-Statement before Committee: Ken Earl: League of Industrial Democracy (Box 63, Folder 982)
  - J-7c-Statement before Committee: Pendleton Herring: Social Science Research Council, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 983)
  - J-7d-Statement before Committee: Sugarman, Dir (Box 63, Folder 984)
  - J-7e-Statement before Committee: Aaron M. Sargent, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 985)
  - J-7f-Statement before Committee: American Council of Learned Societies, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 986)
  - J-7g-Statement before the Committee: Ford Foundation, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 987)
  - J-7h-Statement before the Committee: Fund for the Republic, Inc., 1954 (Box 63, Folder 988)
  - J-7i-Statement before the Committee: Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 989)
  - J-7j-Statement before Committee: League of Industrial Democracy: Laidler, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 990)
  - J-7k-Statement before Committee: Caswell: Teachers College, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 991)
  - J-7l-Statement before Committee: Shafer: American Historical Association, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 992)
  - J-7m-Statement before Committee: Dollard: Carnegie Corporation, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 993)
  - J-7n-Statement before Committee: Nason: Foreign Policy Association, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 994)
  - J-7o-Statement before Committee: Gellhorn, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 995)
  - J-7p-Statement before Committee: Carr: National Education Association, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 996)
  - J-8a-General Correspondence with Committee, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 997)
  - J-8b-Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 63, Folder 998)
  - J-8c-John Dodds-Ettinger and Related Correspondence: Pacific Spectator, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 999)
  - J-8d-Eittinger Letter to Colleges, Etc., with Related Correspondence, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 1000)
  - J-8e-Fowler, Leva, Hawes and Symington: Correspondence Including Reports on Daily Hearings, 1953-1954 (Box 64, Folder 1001)
  - J-8f-Correspondence with Trustees, 1953-1954 (Box 64, Folder 1002)
  - J-8g-Correspondence with Information Services, 1952-1954 (Box 64, Folder 1003)
  - J-8h-Correspondence Dean Rusk and Joint Committee on Internal Revenue Taxation, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 1004)
  - J-9-American Council on Education Meeting with Committee, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 1005)
  - J-10-Possible Questions to be Posed by Committee, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 1006)
  - J-11a-Press Clippings, 1953-1955 (Box 64, Folder 1007)
  - J-11b-Ripley Correspondence: Mainly AP Reports, 1953-1955 (Box 65, Folder 1008A)
  - J-11b-Ripley Correspondence: Mainly AP Reports, 1953-1955 (Box 65, Folder 1008B)
  - J-11c-Reece-Celler TV Appearance on "Facts Forum", 1953 September 7 (Box 65, Folder 1009)
  - J-11c (2)-"The Facts About Facts Forum", 1968 January 4-June 26 (Box 65, Folder 1010)
  - J-11d-Reece-Hays TV Appearance on "The American Week", 1968 July 3-December 24 (Box 65, Folder 1011)
  - J-11e-Publicity From Rockefeller Foundation, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 1012)
  - J-12-"Saturday Review", Artivles on Empirical Research by Odegard and Mills, 1954 (Box 65, Folder 1013)
  - J-13-Charts, 1953-1954 (Box 65, Folder 1014)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. I, 1954 May 10 (Box 65, Folder 1015)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. II, 1954 May 11 (Box 65, Folder 1016)
  - J-14-Reece Committee Transcript, Vol. III, 1954 May 18 (Box 65, Folder 1017)